[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the famous Hungarian cake, called Dobos torte, topped with?", "correct_answer": "Caramel slices", "incorrect_answers": ["Cotton candy", "Chocolate shavings", "Sugar glass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This US President was an instructor in classical languages. Being ambidextrous, he could simultaneously write in Greek with one hand and in Latin with the other.", "correct_answer": "Garfield", "incorrect_answers": ["Chester A. Arthur", "Jefferson", "Teddy Roosevelt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Misses sizes are cut more generously in the bust and hips than junior sizes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which French phrase can mean tastes differ?", "correct_answer": "Chacun a son gout", "incorrect_answers": ["Pret-a-porter", "Pour encourager les autres", "Idee fixe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the United States Census Bureau in 2006, China was the most populated country in the world.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Back to the Future is classified as what kind of movie?", "correct_answer": "Sci-fi comedy", "incorrect_answers": ["Sci-fi", "Drama", "Action"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the 1997 sci-fi horror movie, starring Sam Neil, that takes place in orbit around the planet Neptune?", "correct_answer": "Event Horizon", "incorrect_answers": ["Alien 3", "The Black Hole", "Red Planet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How often should a woman change her bra?", "correct_answer": "every 6 months", "incorrect_answers": ["every 9 months", "every 5 weeks", "once a 1year"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements about echidnas, mammals native to Australia, is wrong?", "correct_answer": "Echidnas are marsupials.", "incorrect_answers": ["Echidnas are covered with spines.", "Echidnas have snouts.", "Echidnas lay eggs."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2005 movie Pizza My Heart was loosely based on this play by William Shakespeare.", "correct_answer": "Romeo and Juliet", "incorrect_answers": ["Twelfth Night", "Much Ado About Nothing", "Othello"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Clueless, what country was the Horowitzs maid Lucy from?", "correct_answer": "El Salvador", "incorrect_answers": ["Mexico", "Panama", "Cuba"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do cats go crazy over catnip?", "correct_answer": "Because it smells like a cat in heat", "incorrect_answers": ["Because it smells like prey", "Because it smells like tasty food", "Because it is an aphrodisiac"]}]